<page>
  <about>
   Back in 1968 a rancher by the name of Lucas Brown decided the life of a cowboy was no longer his passion.
   He decided to get into accounting and start a new life in the big city. Lucas Moved to Manhattan after getting
   his CPA in 1972 and decided to chase his dream of being a successful business man in the big apple. It was there
   where he met his partner Mortimer Schorr, a long time pharmacy shop owner in the lower east side. Mortimer had
   a good standing with the big pharmaceutical companies in Manhattan, but had the savvy of a small business owner.
   In 1976 Maverick Pharmaceutical Accounting was born. Lucas and Mortimer paved the way for a better future and
   forever changed the way accounting was done for the pharmaceutical industry. Maverick has always been about innovation
   and integrity, something that is necessary in the industry. In 1998 Lucas and Mortimer passed down the business to
   their children, Bobby Brown and Maria Schorr, who then took the company into the digital age at the turn of the 
   century. Today Maverick is still a class act, servicing companies big and small, treating each client with the
   up most respect.
  </about>
  <mission>
  Here at Maverick Pharmaceutical Accounting LLC, we aim to please our clients by providing them top quality service
  at an affordable rate. We want all of our clients to feel like they are in good hands at all times.
  When it comes to crunching the numbers, you shouldn't have to worry about that burden. We crunch the numbers for you
  while also providing personal and thorough customer service. We always have representatives working on your caseload.
  We service clients from small businesses all the way up to large conglomerates like AstraZeneca and Novartis.
  No matter your size, we treat you with the up most respect and respond to your problems with expedience. Numbers
  are hard, let us do the heavy lifting for you!
  </mission>
  <contact>
  Maverick Pharmaceutical Accounting LLC is located in the heart of manhattan, on 40th street and 7th avenue.
  We can be reached by phone at 1800-656-2232. All potential client questions can be answered by emailing us
  at mavbiz@maverickpa.com. To ask about becoming a potential associate contact us at mavjobs@maverickpa.com.
  Our offices are open 7 days a week, and our customer support line is extended into 11pm 7 days a week. 
  Our business hours are 8am-9pm every day. We are closed on Thanksgiving, Christmas Day and New Years Day.  
  </contact>
  <picture>
   Here is our Lovely staff.  
  </picture> 
 
</page>